# Jelissa Summers







# **Objective**

To use my ability to navigate and conquer busy high stress environments to ensure your business is both productive and efficient. I have managerial experience overseeing thousands of associates all the while juggling high volume tasks, coordinating with fellow team members to tackle projects, and processing both employee and client inquiries. I hope to apply my administrative skills to be an asset to my team.

### Skills

- Excellent written communication
- o Customer Service
- o Time Management
- Leadership experience
- o Can type 100WPM
- o Organizational Skills
- o Can use Windows/Macintosh operating systems

## **Employment History**

#### JCPenney – Jewelry Sales Associate 10/2021 – current

- o Set up and organize jewelry display in the morning
- o Receive boxes of new jewelry pieces and arrange them within displays
- Display appropriate product signage advertising sales
- o Present jewelry pieces to prospective customers
- o Maintain security of pieces in vault
- o Prepare customer's damaged pieces for send-off at repair facility
- o Sell jewelry care plan packages as well as JCPenney credit cards

## Shift Manger - Amazon Fulfillment (Integrity Staffing Solutions) - 8/2019 - 6/2020

- o Create and Issue job performance and behavioral write-ups
- o Gauge and evaluate associate performance, providing additional training if necessary
- o Recording associate injuries and escalating them to the proper channels
- o Monitor associate attendance and terminate based upon policy
- Assist associates with non-work related injuries and conditions in acquiring accommodations
- O Document and review employee relation issues (e.g. theft, sexual harassment, workplace violence, hostile work environments, breach of security, discrimination, etc.).
- o Document and report hazards in the work environment
- o Coordinate effectively with Amazon HR to bridge production inefficiencies
- Select candidates from a pool of associates for promotion; interviewing, training, and evaluating them accordingly
- o Bridge employee attrition and implement creative ways to drive positive attendance
- o Review and log daily production metrics
- o Reach out to associates and address job related concerns.
- o Resolve and review paycheck issues

#### Dollar General - Cashier (Temp) 4/2016 - 11/2018

- o Utilize cash register to process cash, credit, and debit transactions
- o Work efficiently to reduce line congestion

# Jelissa Summers







- o Stock shelving with product
- o Install promotional banners, posters, and displays
- Maintain presentability of aisles and storefront

#### Placement Specialist – Integrity Staffing Solutions (Temp) – 10/2014 – 11/2015

- o Conduct saliva based drug test and concomitant paperwork to be delivered to LabCorp and verify their accuracy
- o Conduct job interviews to place and schedule applicable recruits in various warehouse positions
- o Bridge recruits on Amazon warehouse policies and procedures,
- o Provide a synopsis of the Amazon warehouse environment
- o Verify requisite I-9 documentation and process it through E-Verify
- o Contact potential recruits and informing them available jobs and placing them on assignments if interested

#### Server Assistant (Longhorn Steakhouse) – 7/2012 – 12/2012

- o Greet customers with a smile
- Seat customers
- o Clean the main lobby and bus tables
- o Answer telephone calls
- o Take to-go orders
- o Direct aspiring applicants to the website
- o Organize and prepare menus
- Set tables
- o Manage and direct large party groups and organize the dining room accordingly

## **Education and Training**

- o Reynolds Community College Richmond, VA Information Systems Technology Web Development Career Certificate 2023
- Highland Springs High School Highland Springs, VA Highschool Diploma 2008